bunzola.com 2007-12-17

# Bunzola Search Engine Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Bunzola is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that kids' information is protected.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Bunzola, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit Bunzola, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Bunzola, and not to other companies or organizations Web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked Bunzola and these branded Web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies.

**Information about all Bunzola's visitors**  
In general, our service automatically gathers certain usage information like the numbers and frequency of visitors to Bunzola and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, Bunzola may use a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. Bunzola cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, never information about you personally, to our Bunzola partners about how our "members", collectively, use Bunzola. We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well. 

**Disclosure**  
We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Bunzola or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. But as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of Bunzola.

**Bunzola privacy policy changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy for Bunzola, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

For additional information, or to express your concerns, please contact [info@bunzola.com](mailto:info@bunzola.com)
